A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1989-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1989-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.921
This collection consists of 15,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1992 September 7.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by Robert O'Neil, the President of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1989-1990; seldom used permanent files, 1972-1991; University committee files, 1989-1990; and, task force files, 1989-1990.
Organization
SERIES I: General Files, 1989-1990 Boxes 1-43
SERIES II: Seldom Used Permanent Files, 1972-1991 Boxes 43-45
SERIES III: University Committees Files, 1989-1990 Box 45-47
SERIES IV: Task Force Files, 1989-1990 Box 47
SERIES V: Restricted Materials, 1989-1990 Box 48
Contents List
- SERIES I: General Records
  - "A" Miscellaneous (1-6 of 9) 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - "A" Miscellaneous (7-9 of 9) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Administration--General 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Computer Services--General 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--General (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Law (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Medical (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs--General 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Alumni--General (Association) and Board of Managers (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Alumni--General (Association) and Board of Managers (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Alumni and Friends Letters 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities--General 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors--General 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - American Bar Association--General 1990 Jan-Jun (Box 3)
  - American Bar Association--General 1989 Jul-Dec (Box 3)
  - American Bar Association Standards for Approval of Law Schools 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education--General 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports--President's Reports 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology--General 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Positions "A-Z" (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Architecture--General 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Art--General 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Art--Arts, Planning and Development for 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Art--Bayly Museum-General 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Asian Studies-General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Associated Western Universities--General 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Colleges--General 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities--General (1-2 of 6) 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities--General (3-6 of 6) 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities--Executive Committee (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities--Spring Meeting-Washington, D.C. 1990 May (Box 5)
  - NASULGC Annual Meeting--Washington, D.C. 1989 Nov (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities--Ann Arbor, Michigan 1989 Oct (Box 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards--General 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Association of Research Libraries--General 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges--General 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Astronomy--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--General (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--General (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--Atlantic Coast Conference 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--College Football Association 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--Finances (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Florida Citrus Bowl 1990 Jan 1 (Box 7)
  - Atlantic Council of the U.S.--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Auditor (Internal)--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts--General 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (5 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Biology--General 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Birdwood--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--Vice Presidential Planning Group (VPPG) (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Business Operations--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (1-4 of 9) 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (5-9 of 9) 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Career Planning and Placement--General 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Cavalier Daily--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (C.I.T.) (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Center for Public Service--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Charlottesville, City of--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Charlottesville, City of (PACC)--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - China--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Civil Rights--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Classics--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Clinch Valley College--General 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - College of Arts and Sciences--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - College Board--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Commerce--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Community Colleges--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Comptroller (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Condolences "A-Z" 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Congress--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--Capital 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--Central Virginia--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--Capital Northern Virginia--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--Capital Tidewater-General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--Capital Valley--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Consortia--Capital Western--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Continuing Education--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Council of Presidents--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Council of Southern Universities--General 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Council of Postsecondary Education Accreditation (COPA) 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business Administration--General 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Darden Business Sponsors--General 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Dean's Meetings--General 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Development-General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Development--Internal Development Group (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Development--"Perspectives" 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Drama--General 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Economics--General 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Education--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Engineering Development Committee--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Engineering and Buildings (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - English--General 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Enrollment--General 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Enrollment (Statistics)--General 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Environmental Statistics 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action--General (1-2 of 3) 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action--General (3 of 3) 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - "F" Miscellaneous (1-5 of 7) (1990 February 22, Arthur Ashe to President O'Neil) 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - "F" Miscellaneous (6-7 of 7) (1990 February 22, Arthur Ashe to President O'Neil) 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Faculty--General 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Faculty--Letter to the Faculty 1990 Mar 12 (Box 17)
  - "Special" Faculty Letter 1989 Oct 9 (Box 17)
  - Faculty Letter 1989 Sep (Box 17)
  - Faculty of Arts of Sciences--General 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Financial Aid to Students--General 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Food Services--General 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - French--General 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 5) 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (4-5 of 5) 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - General Assembly--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - General Assembly--House Appropriations (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - General Assembly--Legislative Summaries 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - General Counsel--General 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - General Services (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - German--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants "A-C" (6 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants "D-G" (7 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Gifts and Grants "H" (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Gifts and Grants "H" (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 21)
  - Gifts and Grants "I-M" (7 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 21)
  - Gifts and Grants "N-T" (8 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Gifts and Grants "U-Z" (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs--General 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governmental Relations--General 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--General 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Administration (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Commerce and Resources (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Decentralization Task Force (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Education 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Finance 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Health and Human Services 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Natural Resources 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Task Force on Science and Technology (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Transportation and Public Safety (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Virginia--Israel Commission (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Washington Liaison Office (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences--General 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (1 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (2-4 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - Harrison Foundation--General 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - History--General 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - Honor System--General 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - Housing--General 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Industrial Relations (University)-General 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Information Technology (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - International Students--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - International Studies--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation--General 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Jefferson Scholars--General 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration Advisory Board (JRAB)--General 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration Advisory Board (JRAB) Committee--Newsletter 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC)--General 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 3) 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (3 of 3) 1989-1990 (Box 27)
  - Law--General 1989-1990 (Box 27)
  - Lawn Policy Use--General 1989-1990 (Box 27)
  - Library--General 1989-1990 (Box 27)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 27)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - "Mf-Mz" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Marine Science 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Mariner's Museum (1-2 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Mariner's Museum (3-4 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 29)
  - Material Management (Purchasing)-General 1989-1990 (Box 29)
  - Mathematics--General 1989-1990 (Box 29)
  - Medical Center--General (1-3 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 29)
  - Medical Center--General (4 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Personnel (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Health Sciences Council 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--General 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Hospital-Personnel (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--General 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Medical School-Personnel (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--General 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--Personnel 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Music--General 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (1-4 of 5) 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (5 of 5) 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - National Association. of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - NASULGC--General (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - NASULGC-- Green Circulars 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - National Science Foundation--General 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Newcomb Hall--General 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - "O" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - "O" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 32)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities--General 1989-1990 (Box 32)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa--General 1989-1990 (Box 32)
  - Online Computer Library Center--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 32)
  - "P" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 32)
  - Parking and Transportation (State)--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Parking--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Personnel--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Personnel and Training (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Philosophy--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Physical Plant--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Physical Plant--Project Status Reports (Construction Reports) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Physics--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Planning--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget (State)--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlays 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget (University of Virginia)--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Poynter Institute--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - President's Staff Meetings (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Promotions (and Tenure)--General 1989-1990 (Box 33)
  - Provost--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Provost--Associate Provost for Research--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Psychology--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - "R" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Real Estate Foundation (UREF)--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Registrar--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Religious Studies--General 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - ROTC--General 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--Army 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--Navy 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (1-6 of 8) 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (7-8 of 8) 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Salaries General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Senate (University)--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures--General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Sociology--General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - South Africa--General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Southern Regional Education Board--General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Space and Energy Management--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Spanish, Italian, and Portuguese--General 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Sponsored Programs--General 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE)--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE)--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE)--Commission on the University of the 21st Century 1989-1990 (Box 37)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE)--Assessment (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Student Affairs-General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - State Council of Higher Education--Council Notes 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - State Council of Higher Education--On Line 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - State Department of Education--General 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - State Fire Marshall--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Student Affairs--General 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Student Council (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Student Council (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Student Council Minutes 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Summer Session--General 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - "Ta-Te" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - "Tf-Tz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Travel Invoices 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Treasurer (State)--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - United States Savings Bond 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - United Way (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Universities Research Association--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Business Innovation Center--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Guide Service--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Journal--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Police--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Press of Virginia--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Relations--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - University Union--General 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Middle School Association 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Military Institute 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute University 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Port Authority 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Regional Minor Supplier Development Council 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Rowing Association 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Scholar's Program 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Virginia School Boards Association 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Science Museum 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Sil'hooettes 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Space Grant 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia State Fair 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia State Library 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia State University 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Symposium in Medieval Studies 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - The Virginia Tax Review Service 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Transportation Conference 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Community College System 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Engineering Foundation 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Bar Association 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Academy of Science--General 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film--General 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Judicial System Commission--General 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review--General (empty) 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Vouchers (1 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - Vouchers (2 of 2) 1989-1990 (Box 42)
  - "Wa-Wh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 42)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (1 of 3) 1989-1990 (Box 42)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (2-3 of 3) 1989-1990 (Box 43)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous 1989-1990 (Box 43)
- SERIES II: Seldom Used Permanent Files
  - General Counsel--White, Larry 1989-1991 (Box 43)
  - King, John H. 1976-1988 (Box 43)
  - Lawn Society--October 1989 Meeting 1989-1989 (Box 43)
  - Legal Adviser 1989-1989 (Box 43)
  - Legal Adviser--George G. Grattan, IV (1-2 of 3) 1972-1988 (Box 43)
  - Legal Adviser--George G. Grattan, IV (3 of 3) 1972-1988 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center--Muller William, H. (Dr.) 1985-1990 (Box 44)
  - Miller Center--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Physical Planning (Shutts) 1976-1980 (Box 44)
  - Visitor's General (1-2 of 5) 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Visitor's General (3-5 of 5) 1988-1989 (Box 45)
- SERIES III: University Committees
  - General 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Arboretum and Landscape 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Athletic Advisory Council 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Calendar 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Community Colleges 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Computing and Communications 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Development Policy 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Dining Services 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1989-1990 (Box 45)
  - Faculty Benefits 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Financial Aid 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Housing 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - International Students 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Judicial Policy 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Libraries 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Master Planning Council 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Names 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Proxy Advisory 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Radiation Safety 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Residential Life 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Scheduling 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Security and General Safety 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Traffic Appeals 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Transportation and Parking 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Undergraduate Admissions 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - University Press of Virginia 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - University Research Policy Advisory 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Women's Concerns 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Vice President's Committees 1989-1990 (Box 46)
- SERIES IV: Task Force
  - University Press 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Use of University Resources 1989-1990 (Box 46)
- SERIES V: Restricted Files (Box 48)